Guide to the Stanford University, Capital Planning and Management, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Training Task Force Report 1991 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Provost Committee on Housing (Box 15, Folder 20)
- COFHE (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Bacchetti - Trustee Vote (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Information Systems Architecture (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Land Use Coordination with SMC (Box 15, Folder 24)
- General Use Permit Annual Report 3 1990-1991 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Domestic Partners Benefits Parity (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Associate Dean in Humanities and Sciences (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Facilities Transition (Box 15, Folder 28)
- UPPM Report 1991 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Hughes (John L. Hughes, Vice Provost of Planning and Management) Chronological 8-12/1985 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Hughes Chronological 1-7/1986 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Hughes Chronological 8-12/1986 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Medical Center Regional Plan Update 1988 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Medical Center Regional Plan 11/1988 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Medical Center Annual Fact Book 1989 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Medical Center Extended Summary of Report of Institutional Planning Committee 4/1989 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Advanced Materials Research Building ADEIR, FEIR (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Center for Integrated Systems Feasibility Study 1988 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Santa Clara County General Use Plan, FEIR 5/1989 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Safety Funding 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- NWC Hazardous Materials Building (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Physical Condition Survey Report for electronics Research Laboratory (Box 16, Folder 13)
- SU Annual Financial Reports 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Operating Budget Guidelines 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Hughes - Miscellaneous Correspondence 1989 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Medical Center Annual Fact Book 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Health and Safety 1988 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- IIT (Illinois Institute of Technology) Project 21 1989 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- School of Medicine Planning Commission Working Group Report 1988 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Decanal Indirect Cost Study 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Academic Staff Handbook 1975 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Affirmative Action Report 1988 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Regional Planning Report 1988 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Faculty Handbook 1984 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Operation Budget Guidelines1988-89 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Proposed Building Plans 1988-2000 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Research Policy Handbook 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Faculty Retirement Information (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Stanford Staff Benefit Rate 1990 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Course Enrollment Summary 1987-88 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- HR Affirmative Action Hiring Administrators at SU 1975 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- HR Affirmative Action Staff Annual Data 1978 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- HR Affirmative Action Goals 1981 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- HR Affirmative Action Plan 1983 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- HR Affirmative Action Anticipated Vacancies 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- HR Affirmative Action End of Year Progress Report 1983 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Budget - Kent Peterson Information 1980-1981 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Budget - Salary Budgeting New Methodology and New Reserves 1981 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Budget - Salary Budgeting Recommendations 1980 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Budget - President/Provost Salary Book 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Facilities - 01-310 Seismic Strengthening 1990-1991 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Facilities - 01-320 Seismic Strengthening 1990-1991 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Facilities - 01-360 1990-1991 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Facilities - 01-370 Seismic Strengthening 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Facilities - 01-420 Psych 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Facilities - 01-460 Margaret Jacks Hall 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Facilities - 01-500 Memorial Church 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Facilities - 01-500 Clubhouse Auditorium 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Facilities - 01-535 Solar Observatory Equipment Shed 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- CEFA (California Educational Facilities Authority) Series F Official Statement (Box 18, Folder 7)
- CEFA BOT Agenda Item 1984 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- CEFA 1984 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- CEFA Financing Team Roster 1984 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous Budget, HR, etc. Mickey Murray (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Allocable Costs 1986 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- NWC Background Data (Box 18, Folder 13)
- NWC Program Notebook (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Centennial Planning (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Centennial Campaign - Key Documents (Box 18, Folder 16)
- NWC Planning Group 1986 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- HR Affirmative Action Plan 1978-1980 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- HR Affirmative Action Staff Planning Package 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- HR Benefits Recommendations, Progress Report and Budget 1983 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- HR Performance Communication Workshop 1984 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- HR Affirmative Action Seminar (Box 18, Folder 22)
- HR Affirmative Action 1974, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- HR Affirmative Action 1973 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- HR Affirmative Action 1984 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- HR Personnel Task Force 1983 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- HR Salaries 1979 (Box 18, Folder 27)
- HR Salary Budgeting 1981 (Box 18, Folder 28)
- HR Affirmative Action 1984 (Box 18, Folder 29)
- HR Employment Decentralization 1979 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- HR Employment/Recruitment 1981 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Budget 1980-1981 - Admissions (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Budget 1980-1981 - CRIS (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Budget 1980-1981 - DAPER (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Budget 1980-1981 - Dean of Student Affairs (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Budget 1980-1981 - Development (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Budget 1980-1981 - Earth Sciences (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Budget 1980-1981 - Education (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Budget 1980-1981 - Engineering (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Budget 1980-1981 - Graduate Financial Aid (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Budget 1980-1981 - Undergraduate Financial Aid (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Budget 1980-1981 - Graduate School of Business (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Budget 1980-1981 - Graduate Studies (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Budget 1980-1981 - Hopkins Marine Station (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Budget 1980-1981 - Hoover Institution (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Budget 1980-1981 - Humanities and Sciences (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Budget 1980-1981 - Independent Labs and Institutes (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Budget 1980-1981 - Libraries (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Budget 1980-1981 - Medicine (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Budget 1980-1981 - Memorial Church (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Budget 1980-1981 - Overseas Studies (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Budget 1980-1981 - President/ Provost's Office (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Budget 1980-1981 - University Press (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Budget 1980-1981 - Public Affairs (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Budget 1980-1981 - Registrar (Box 19, Folder 26)
- Budget 1980-1981 - SLIP (Box 19, Folder 27)
- Budget 1980-1981 - SLAC (Box 19, Folder 28)
- Budget 1980-1981 - Summer Session (Box 19, Folder 29)
- Budget 1980-1981 - Undergraduate Studies (Box 19, Folder 30)
- Budget 1980-1981 - University Counsel (Box 19, Folder 31)
- Budget 1980-1981 - Values, Technology and Society (Box 19, Folder 32)
- Budget 1980-1981 - Western Culture Program (Box 19, Folder 33)
- Budget 1982-1983 - Admissions (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Budget 1982-1983 - Business and Finance (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Budget 1982-1983 - DAPER (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Budget 1982-1983 - Dean of Student Affairs (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Budget 1982-1983 - Development (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Budget 1982-1983 - Earth Sciences (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Budget 1982-1983 - Education (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Budget 1982-1983 - Engineering (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Budget 1982-1983 - Graduate Financial Aid (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Budget 1982-1983 - Undergraduate Financial Aid (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Budget 1982-1983 - Graduate School of Business (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Budget 1982-1983 - Graduate Studies (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Budget 1982-1983 - Hoover Institution (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Budget 1982-1983 - Humanities and Sciences (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Budget 1982-1983 - Independent Labs and Institutes (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Budget 1982-1983 - Law School (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Budget 1982-1983 - LOTS (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Budget 1982-1983 - Libraries (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Budget 1982-1983 - Medicine (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Budget 1982-1983 - Memorial Church (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Budget 1982-1983 - Overseas Studies (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Budget 1982-1983 - President/ Provost's Office (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Budget 1982-1983 - University Press (Box 20, Folder 23)
- Budget 1982-1983 - Public Affairs (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Budget 1982-1983 - Registrar (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Budget 1982-1983 - SLAC (Box 20, Folder 26)
- Budget 1982-1983 - Summer Session (Box 20, Folder 27)
- Budget 1982-1983 - University Counsel (Box 20, Folder 28)
- Budget 1982-1983 - Western Culture Program (Box 20, Folder 29)
- Budget 1982-1983 - Indirect Cost Rates and Recovery 1983 (Box 20, Folder 30)
- HR Pluralism (Box 20, Folder 31)
- NWC Reference Notebook for Futures (Box 20, Folder 32)
- NWC Key Documents (Box 21, Folder 1)
- NWC Fundraising and Building Cost Info (Box 21, Folder 2)
- HR Affirmative Action 1981-1982 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- HR Affirmative Action Mid-year OFCCP Report 1982 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- HR Affirmative Action 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- HR Affirmative Action Mid-year OFCCP Report 1981 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- HR Affirmative Action 1982 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Survey of Directors of Institutes, Centers, and Independent Labs 1985 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Vice-Presidential Area Plans for Achieving Pluralism (Box 21, Folder 9)
- HR UCMI Staff Subcommittee Native Americans (Box 21, Folder 10)
- HR Repositioning (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Housing - Provost Committee on Housing 1989 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Facilities - Quad 7 General (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Facilities - 07-10/20/30 East Med Science Bldg Medical Microbiology (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Facilities - 07-25 Parking Structure I (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Facilities - 07-30X Medical Microbiology (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Facilities - 07-100 Cantor Sculpture Garden (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Facilities - 07-130 Gates of Hell (Work of Art) (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Facilities - 07-200 Chemistry - Nuts and Mudd (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Facilities - 07-210 Seeley G. Mudd Chemistry (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Facilities - 07-220 Laboratory Surge Building (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Facilities - 07-250 Organic Chemistry (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Facilities - 07-250 Keck Bio Space Agreement (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Facilities – (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Facilities - 07-300 Medical Center (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Facilities - 07-320 Medical Center - Central Core (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Facilities - 07-303 Medical Center West Pavilion (Box 21, Folder 27)
- Facilities - 07-304 Medical Center East Pavilion (Box 21, Folder 28)
- Facilities - 07-305 Boswell Clinics (Box 21, Folder 29)
- Facilities - 07-306 Medical Center Grant Building (Box 21, Folder 30)
- Facilities - 07-307 Medical Center Medical Building (Box 21, Folder 31)
- Facilities - 07-308 Medical Center Lane Building (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Facilities - 07-309 Edwards Building (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Facilities - 07-310 Hospital Modernization Project (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Facilities - 07-315 Packard's New Children's Hospital (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Facilities - 07-320 Cardiovascular Research Building (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Facilities - 07-330 Research Animal Facility I (under construction) (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Facilities - 07-400 Herrin Labs - Biology (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Facilities - 07-405 Human Biology (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Facilities - 07-420 Gilbert Biology (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Facilities - 07-420T Herrin Biology Modulars (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Facilities - 07-520 Fairchild (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Facilities - 07-530 Beckman Center (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Facilities - 07-560 MSOB (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Facilities - 07-570 Med School Lab Surge (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Facilities - 07-997T Interim Waste Facility (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Facilities - 07-580 Medical Center Parking (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Facilities - 07-970 Psychology Clinic (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Regional Planning 1986 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Regional Planning 1987 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Regional Planning 1988 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Facilities Plan and Funding Forecast 1983-1986 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Mayfield School Site (Box 22, Folder 22)
- NWC 1989-1990 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Operations and Management 1990-1991 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Parking Structure III (Box 22, Folder 25)
- Planned Maintenance (Box 22, Folder 26)
- Salary Settings 1985-87 (Box 22, Folder 27)
- Salary Settings 1986-87 (Box 22, Folder 28)
- Budget Process and Planning Parameters for 1991-1993 1990-91 (Box 22, Folder 29)
- Long Range Budget Planning Parameters, 1989-90, 1991-1992 (Box 22, Folder 30)
- Resumes for Executive VP of JCEE (Box 22, Folder 31)
- HR Response to UMCI Report 1989 (Box 22, Folder 32)
- Claire Phillips Chronological (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Facilities - Stanford West 1978-1982 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Facilities - GPI 1978-1990 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Facilities - Searsville Block 1986 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Facilities - (Box 23, Folder 5)
- EQ (Earthquake Files) FEMA General Correspondence (Box 23, Folder 6)
- EQ FEMA Email Correspondence (Box 23, Folder 7)
- EQ FEMA Office of Emergency Services (Box 23, Folder 8)
- EQ FEMA Facilities Project Management Earthquake Damage Report (Box 23, Folder 9)
- EQ FEMA Stanford Building (Box 23, Folder 10)
- EQ FEMA Memorandum (Box 23, Folder 11)
- EQ FEMA Facilities Project Management Correspondence (Box 23, Folder 12)
- EQ FEMA Facilities Project Management Approvals 12/1990 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Palo Alto Planning - Menlo Park General Plan Circular (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Palo Alto Planning - Page Mill - El Camino Intersection 1975-1978 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Palo Alto Planning - Stanford University (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Palo Alto Planning - Sand Hill Corridor (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Facilities Planning - Psych Facility 1986-1987 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Facilities Planning - Quarry Road (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Facilities Planning - Reagan Library (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Facilities Planning - Ryan Lab Site Housing (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Facilities Planning - Serra Complex (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Facilities Planning - Site Analysis (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Facilities Planning - Space Issues (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Facilities Planning - Stanford Land Use (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Facilities Planning - Stanford West (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Facilities Planning - Student Housing (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Facilities Planning - Graduate Student Housing (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Facilities Planning - New Student Housing (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Facilities Planning - San Francisquito Creek (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Facilities Planning - Searsville Lake (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Facilities Planning - Transportation Program (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Facilities Planning - Transportation (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Facilities Planning - TDM Transportation Demand Management (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Facilities Planning - Undergraduate Housing Project (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Facilities Planning - Utilities and Systems (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Facilities Planning - Washington D.C. Campus 1987 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Facilities Planning - Local Jurisdictions (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Facilities Planning - Junipero Serra Blvd. Discussions (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Facilities Planning - Santa Clara County General Use Plan 1989 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Facilities Planning - Oak Creek 1981-1985 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Facilities Planning - Pearce Mitchell 1983-1987 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Facilities Planning - Peter Coutts Hill 1979-1989 (Box 24, Folder 24)
- Facilities Planning - Westin Stanford (Box 24, Folder 25)
- Facilities Planning - Stanford in Washington (Box 25, Folder 1)
- NWC Visit to Walt Disney World (Box 25, Folder 2)
- NWC The Architect's Collective (Box 25, Folder 3)
- NWC "Three Alternatives" Framing Advice (Box 25, Folder 4)
- HR Council Agendas, Minutes and Notes (Box 25, Folder 5)
- HR Staff Agendas 1988 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- NWC Planning Staff Agendas 1987 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- NWC Planning Staff Agendas 1982-1984 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- NWC Planning Updates (Box 25, Folder 9)
- NWC Academic Support Services (Box 25, Folder 10)
- NWC Thomas Allen Visit (Box 25, Folder 11)
- NWC Academic Working Groups (Box 25, Folder 12)
- NWC Administration Council Presentations (Box 25, Folder 13)
- NWC Articles (Box 25, Folder 14)
- NWC Biotech Processing (Box 25, Folder 15)
- NWC Centennial Grove (Box 25, Folder 16)
- NWC Consultants (Box 25, Folder 17)
- NWC Critical Path Task Meetings (Box 25, Folder 18)
- NWC Endowed Chairholders (Box 25, Folder 19)
- NWC Futures (Box 25, Folder 20)
- NWC Fundraising Strategies (Box 25, Folder 21)
- NWC Fundraising - Landscaping (Box 25, Folder 22)
- NWC General (Box 25, Folder 23)
- NWC Glossary 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- NWC Implementation (Box 25, Folder 25)
- NWC Managing the Academic Region (Box 25, Folder 26)
- NWC Managing the NWC Campus (Box 26, Folder 1)
- NWC Organizational Chart (Box 26, Folder 2)
- NWC Program Document Draft (Box 26, Folder 3)
- NWC Publicity (Box 26, Folder 4)
- NWC Recycling Border Buildings (Box 26, Folder 5)
- NWC Safety and Code (Box 26, Folder 6)
- NWC Senate Discussion 4/1986 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- NWC Space General (Box 26, Folder 8)
- NWC SPRC (Box 26, Folder 9)
- NWC Staff Assistant (Box 26, Folder 10)
- NWC Staffing Levels (Box 26, Folder 11)
- NWC Student Survey (Box 26, Folder 12)
- NWC Service and Circulation (Box 26, Folder 13)
- NWC Utilities (Box 26, Folder 14)
- NWC GPI (Box 26, Folder 15)
- NWC Working Groups (Box 26, Folder 16)
- NWC Working Partner Dialogues (Box 26, Folder 17)
- NWC Work Plan (Box 26, Folder 18)
- NWC Occupancy/Use Survey (Box 26, Folder 19)
- NWC Academic Protocols (Box 26, Folder 20)
- NWC Architect's Collective (Box 26, Folder 21)
- NWC Physical Planning (Box 26, Folder 22)
- NWC Statement of Principles (Box 26, Folder 23)
- NWC Space Types and Characteristics (Box 26, Folder 24)
- NWC Futures (Box 26, Folder 25)
- NWC Miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 26)
- HR Affirmative Action Report 1988 (Box 26, Folder 27)
- HR Council Minority Intern Program (Box 26, Folder 28)
- HR Council Professional Development Options (Box 26, Folder 29)
- HR Council Organization (Box 26, Folder 30)
- HR Council Employee Referral (Box 26, Folder 31)
- HR Council Affirmative Action Awards (Box 26, Folder 32)
- HR Council Budget and Funding (Box 26, Folder 33)
- HR Council Retirement Plan Design (Box 26, Folder 34)
- HR Council Compensation Proposal 1988-1989 (Box 26, Folder 35)
- HR Council Compensation Proposal 1987-1988 (Box 26, Folder 36)
- HR Council Retirement Planning (Box 26, Folder 37)
- HR Council Office of Planning and Management Briefing 12/1987 (Box 26, Folder 38)
- HR Council Joel Henning 1989 (Box 26, Folder 39)
- HR Reorganization (Box 26, Folder 40)
- NWC Management Meetings (Box 26, Folder 41)
- NWC Repositioning (Box 26, Folder 42)
- Subcommittee on IDCR (Indirect Cost Rate) 1990 (Box 26, Folder 43)
- CIS Extension Regional Facilities (Box 26, Folder 44)
- CIS Extension South Service Road (Box 26, Folder 45)
- CIS Extension Information Science (Box 26, Folder 46)
- CIS Extension Statistics (Box 26, Folder 47)
- CIS Extension North Service Road (Box 26, Folder 48)
- NWC Utilities (Box 26, Folder 49)
- NWC December Gift (Box 27, Folder 1)
- NWC Electronic Communications (Box 27, Folder 2)
- NWC Sallie Mae (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Earthquake Modulars (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Cost of Buildings study (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Operations and Maintenance "Before the Roof Caves In" Report (Box 27, Folder 6)
- BOT Ad Hoc Budget Advisory Group (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Facilities - Quad 1 General 1988-1991 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Facilities - Main Quad Design Guidelines (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Facilities - Arcades Earthquake (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Facilities - 01-001 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Facilities - Arcades - Inner Quad (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Facilities - Arcades - Quad East (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Facilities - 01-030 Earthquake (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Facilities - 01-040 Interior Upgrade (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Facilities - 01-060 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Facilities - 01-080 Surge (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Facilities - 01-160 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Facilities - 01-170 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- Facilities - 01-210 Rodin Sculpture (Box 27, Folder 20)
- Facilities - 01-260 Languages (Box 27, Folder 21)
- Facilities - 01-260 Languages (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Facilities - 01-300 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Facilities - Quad 4 General (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Facilities - 04-240 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Facilities - 04-200 Ginzton (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Facilities - 04-250 HEPL (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Facilities - 04-350/400 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Facilities - 04-460 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Facilities - 04-490 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Facilities - Physics Task Force I and II (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Facilities - 04-520/530 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Facilities - 04-244 Varian Hood Study (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Facilities - 04-540 Durand (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Facilities - 04-560 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Facilities - 04-700 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Facilities - 04-930T Boys Town (Box 28, Folder 16)
- Facilities - Quad 2 General (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Facilities - 02-500 Series (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Facilities - 02-300 Tresidder (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Facilities - 02-300 Copy Center (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Facilities - 02-020 CERAS (Box 28, Folder 21)
- Facilities - 02-400 Bechtel (Box 28, Folder 22)
- Facilities - 02-500 (Box 28, Folder 23)
- Facilities - 02-600 (Box 28, Folder 24)
- Facilities - 02-520/530/540 (Box 28, Folder 25)
- Facilities - 02-550 (Box 28, Folder 26)
- Facilities - 02-560 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Facilities - 02-570 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Facilities - 02-580/590/585/600 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Facilities - 02-610 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Facilities - 02-630 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Facilities - 02-635 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Facilities - 02-650 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Facilities - 02-916 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Facilities - 02-917 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Facilities - 02-914/920/925/926/930 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Facilities - Quad 5 General (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Facilities - 05-106/100/010, Lake House (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Facilities - 05-200/300 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Facilities - 05-250 Boathouse (Box 29, Folder 14)
- EQ Medical Center Seismic Risk Assessment 4/1989 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- EQ Seismic Risk Assessment (Box 29, Folder 16)
- EQ Classroom Improvement (Box 29, Folder 17)
- EQ Seismic Funding Proposals 1986-1988 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- EQ Risk Management Program (Box 29, Folder 19)
- EQ Base Isolation (Box 29, Folder 20)
- EQ BOT Seismic Presentation (Box 29, Folder 21)
- EQ Seismic Instrumentation (Box 29, Folder 22)
- EQ Bendimerad Appointment 1987-1988 (Box 29, Folder 23)
- EQ Risk Financing (Box 29, Folder 24)
- EQ Safety and Code (Box 29, Folder 25)
- EQ Cluster III (Box 29, Folder 26)
- EQ KZSU Emergency Transmitter (Box 29, Folder 27)
- EQ (Box 29, Folder 28)
- EQ ESF (Box 29, Folder 29)
- EQ Seismic Budget (Box 29, Folder 30)
- Regional Plan West Campus 1985 (Box 29, Folder 31)
- Regional Plan Hopkins (Box 29, Folder 32)
- Regional Plan Bonair (Box 29, Folder 33)
- Regional Plan Facilities (Box 29, Folder 34)
- Regional Plan Foothills 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Regional Plan Foothills Junipera Serra 1987 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Regional Plan Foothills Reagan Library (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Regional Plan Hopkins Marine Station (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Regional Plan Civic Center (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Regional Plan Research Park (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Regional Plan Quad Space (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Regional Plan Jordan Quad (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Regional Plan Administrative Space (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Regional Plan Library Space Needs (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Regional Plan New Building Prospectus (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Regional Plan Main Quad Chilled Water (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Regional Plan Medical Center (Box 30, Folder 13)
- Medical School Facilities Planning Clinical Sciences Space (Box 30, Folder 14)
- Medical School Facilities Planning Project Status Report (Box 30, Folder 15)